edgar-online.com 2008-09-15

# EDGAR Online

  | 

### Investor Guide

  * About EDGAR Online
  * Earnings Releases
  * Press Releases 
  * In The News
  * Conference Calls
  * Stock Quote
  * Historical Chart
  * Executive Management
  * Board of Directors
  * Code of Conduct
  * Code of Ethics - CEO
  * Code of Ethics - CFO
  * Charter

|   |  **PRIVACY POLICY**

**_EDGAR Online, Inc._** ("EOL") respects your right to privacy while using our web sites. Our privacy policy detailed below explains what information we may gather from your visit to our web sites and how such information may be used. 

**1\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION.**

Before you utilize our information services, we may ask you to complete a registration web page which requests certain contact information. If you choose to sign up for or purchase a subscription license to EOL Services, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address. We use this information to process your service requests as well as for additional purposes such as tailoring future requests and correspondences, to ensure proper billing, to ask that you participate in online surveys or to register you on a mailing list. We may also collect demographic information, such as your zip code, , preferences, company and business type. Upon your request, EOL will remove your name from any mail or email list through which you registered with us. 

We may also send you information about our additional products and services and, on occasion, share your email address with our select partners so that they may send you relevant product and service offers as well. In addition, we may use your IP address in cooperation with your Internet service provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use agreement for our services, to protect our services or customers, or comply with laws or regulations. We may access and/or disclose your personal information to comply with legal process served on EOL or act in urgent circumstances to protect users of EOL services or members of the public.

**2\. PROTECTION OF INFORMATION.**

Protecting your personal information is important to us. We will take reasonable technical measures to prevent loss or unintended use of your information.

**3\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES.**

Some of our web sites offer links to other web sites that may request and collect your personal contact information. Your use of and provision of such information to these sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such other sites. EOL is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or content of such sites. 

**4\. ADVERTISEMENTS AND USE OF COOKIES.**

Many of the online advertisements you see on our site are displayed by us. However, we allow third-party ad serving providers, including ad networks, to display advertisements on EOL web pages. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by a web page server for identification. EOL or Ad serving providers often place a cookie on you computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an advertisement to you. This information may be used for customization the next time you visit our web sites or make predictions about your characteristics and to display targeted ads that these providers believe may be of interest to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. By not accepting cookies, some pages of our and our third-party ad serving providers web sites, may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on our web sites. Third-party ad serving providers may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting based on their cookies. You may find more information by following the links to the websites of each company. Some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member providers. 

**5\. MODIFICATION OF THIS POLICY:**

EOL reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter, or otherwise revise this privacy policy at any time without notice and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, and revisions. 

Last posting: January, 2008 

To Top

|
